<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Roque_LabAct_4</string>
    <string-array name="verTitle">
        <item>ICBC</item>
        <item>JP Morgan Chase</item>
        <item>China Construction Bank</item>
        <item>Agricultural Bank of China</item>
        <item>Bank Of America</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="verCountry">
        <item>Country: China</item>
        <item>Country: United States</item>
        <item>Country: China</item>
        <item>Country: China</item>
        <item>Country: United States</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="verIndustry">
        <item>Industry: Major Banks</item>
        <item>Industry: none</item>
        <item>Industry: Major Banks</item>
        <item>Industry: Regional Banks</item>
        <item>Industry: Major Banks</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="verCeo">
        <item>CEO: Shu Gu</item>
        <item>CEO: Jamie Dimon</item>
        <item>CEO: Wang Zuji</item>
        <item>CEO: Huan Zhao</item>
        <item>CEO: Brian Moynihan</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="verSum">
    <item>Industrial and Commercial Bank of China Ltd. engages in the provision of commercial banking and financial services.
        It operates through the following business segments: Corporate Banking, Personal Banking, Treasury Operations, and Others.</item>

    <item>JPMorgan Chase and Co. is a financial holding company, which provides financial and investment banking services.
        It offers a range of investment banking products and services in all major capital markets, including advising on corporate strategy and structure; capital-raising
        in equity and debt markets; sophisticated risk management; market-making in cash securities and derivative instruments; and prime brokerage and research.</item>

    <item>China Construction Bank Corp. engages in the provision of financial and banking services.
        It operates through the following segments: Corporate Banking, Personal Banking, Treasury Business, and Others.
        The Corporate Banking segment includes credit businesses, institutional business services, fund settlement and custody, and corporate e-banking.</item>

    <item>Agricultural Bank of China engages in the provision of international commercial banking and financial services.
        The company operates its business through the following segments: Corporate Banking, Personal Banking, Treasury Operations and Others and Unallocated.
        The Corporate Banking segment provides financial products and services to corporations, government agencies and financial institutions. </item>

    <item>Bank of America Corp. is a bank and financial holding company, which engages in the provision of banking and nonbank financial services.
        It operates through the following segments: Consumer Banking, Global Wealth and Investment Management, Global Banking, Global Markets, and Legacy Assets and Servicing.
        The Consumer Banking segment offers credit, banking, and investment products and services to consumers and small businesses.</item>

    </string-array>s













</resources>
